Sexual Violence in Prisons and Jails Reported by Inmates, 2008-09          NCJ   231169				


This zip archive contains tables in individual .csv spreadsheets				
from Sexual Violence in Prisons and Jails Reported by Inmates, 2008-09   NCJ  231169.  
The full report including text and graphics in pdf format is available at: 
http://bjs.ojp.usdoj.gov/index.cfm?ty=pbdetail&iid=2202			



This report is associated with the PREA Data Collection.
For a list of related publications 
go to http://bjs.ojp.usdoj.gov/index.cfm?ty=dcdetail&iid=278

Tables		

svpjri0809t01.csv Table 1. Inmates reporting sexual victimization, by type of facility and incident, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t02.csv Table 2. Facilities with high rates of inmate-on-inmate sexual victimization, by type of facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t03.csv Table 3. Facilities with high rates of staff sexual misconduct, by type of facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t04.csv Table 4. Facilities with low rates of any type of sexual victimization, by type of facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t05.csv Table 5. Rates of sexual victimization in special correctional facilities, by type of incident and facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t06.csv Table 6. Prevalence of sexual victimization, by type of incident and demographic inmate characteristic, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t07.csv Table 7. Multivariate logistic regression models of sexual victimization, by inmate demographic characteristic, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t08.csv Table 8. Prevalence of sexual victimization, by type of incident and sexual history, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t09.csv Table 9. Multivariate logistic models of sexual victimization, by sexual history, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t10.csv Table 10. Prevalence of sexual victimization, by type of incident and criminal justice status, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t11.csv Table 11. Multivariate logistic models of sexual victimization, by criminal justice status and history, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t12.csv Table 12. Final multivariate logistic models of sexual victimization in prisons and jails, by type of incident, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t13.csv Table 13. Estimated and predicted rates of inmate-on-inmate sexual victimization in high-rate prisons and jails, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t14.csv Table 14. Estimated and predicted rates of staff sexual misconduct in high rate prisons and jails, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t15.csv Table 15. Experiences of victims of inmate-on-inmate victims of sexual victimization, by type of facility and sex, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09
svpjri0809t16.csv Table 16. Circumstances surrounding inmate-on-inmate sexual victimization, by type of facility and sex, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t17.csv Table 17. Circumstances surrounding incidents of staff sexual misconduct, by type of facility and sex of victim, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t18.csv Table 18. Sex of perpetrator of staff sexual misconduct, by facility type and sex of victim, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809t19.csv Table 19. Sexual touching between inmates and staff during and not during strip searches and pat downs, by sex of victim, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09

Appendix tables	
	
svpjri0809at01.csv Appendix Table 1. Characteristics of state and federal prisons and prevalence of sexual victimization, by facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09
svpjri0809at02.csv Appendix Table 2. Percent of prison inmates reporting sexual victimization, by type of incident and facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809at03.csv Appendix Table 3. Percent of prison inmates reporting sexual victimization by level of coercion and facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09
svpjri0809at04.csv Appendix Table 4. Percent of prison inmates reporting nonconsensual sexual acts and abusive sexual contacts, by facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09
svpjri0809at05.csv Appendix Table 5. Characteristics of jails and prevalence of sexual victimization, by facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09
svpjri0809at06.csv Appendix Table 6. Percent of jail inmates reporting victimization, by type of incident and facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09
svpjri0809at07.csv Appendix Table 7. Percent of jail inmates reporting sexual victimization, by level of coercion and facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09 
svpjri0809at08.csv Appendix Table 8. Percent of jail inmates reporting nonconsensual sexual acts and abusive sexual contacts, by facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09
svpjri0809at09.csv Appendix Table 9. Characteristics of special correctional facilities and prevalence of sexual victimization, by facility, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09
svpjri0809at10.csv Appendix Table 10. Wald F statistics for inmate risk characteristics in the final multivariate logistic models of sexual victimization in prisons and jails, by type of incident, National Inmate Survey, 2008-09